

PAOLANTONIO DIEGO GABRIEL

Córdoba, Argentina +54 9 351 754 3947 paolantonio.diego@gmail.com

LINKS

SKILLS

HTML CSS BOOTSTRAP SASS JavaScript React JS Node JS GitHub FrontEnd Development **React Native**

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native English – Intermediate Portuguese - Intermediate

ABOUT ME

I am electronic engineer, I studied at Universidad Tecnológica Nacional FRC, with extensive experience in industrial automation, I am making a job change, I always liked programming, which is why I am training as a Full Stack Developer, my goal is be able towork as a developer and continue training in its different branches.

EXPERIENCE

CODERHOUSE - Practica profesional June 2023 - September 2023 React Frontend Developer

Responsabilidades: Program a landing page in React Js for the company INGEMMA.

Freelancer

June 2022 - Present

Electronic Engineer / Automatist

 $\textbf{Responsibilities} : \textbf{Technical assistance} \cdot \textbf{PLC Programming} \cdot \textbf{Electrical design} \cdot \textbf{Project}$ $management \cdot Technical \ management \cdot Team \ management \cdot Process \ automation.$

CORAUTOMATICA SRL

May 2014 - May 2022

Partner / Electronic Engineer / Automatist.

 $\textbf{Responsibilities} : \textbf{Technical assistance} \cdot \textbf{PLC Programming} \cdot \textbf{Electrical design} \cdot \textbf{Project}$ $management \cdot Technical \ management \cdot Team \ management \cdot Process \ automation.$

BETONMAC

Jule 2013 - May 2014

Developer

Responsibilities: Automatic systems Develoment for the production of concrete. Printed Circuit Board Design (PCB), PLC programming, C/C++ programming ofAtMega microcontrollers

EDUCATION

APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

CODERHOUSE, Argentina August 2023 - Present

React JS: React Native, Expo, Firebase.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CODERHOUSE, Argentina

Jule 2022 - August 2023

- Web Development: HTML, CSS, Flexbox, Grid, SASS, BOOTSTRAP,
- JavaScript: JavaScript, DOM, JSON, Node JS, File System.
- React JS: React JS, API's, Firebase.
- BackEnd Programming: JavaScript, File System, MongoDB, Mongoose, express, passport y otros.

ELECTRONIC ENGINEER

UNIVERSIDAD TECNOLÓGICA NACIONAL FRC, Córdoba, Argentina 2004 - 2015